Two Worlds - One New Adventure!
Tarzan & Jane is a animation, family film directed by Steve Loter.
With the first anniversary of her wedding to Tarzan beckoning, Jane
ponders how to make it the perfect English celebration.
Tarzan (voice), played by Michael T. Weiss.
Jane Porter (voice), played by Olivia D'Abo.
Prof. Archimedes Q. Porter (voice), played by Jeff Bennett.
Tantor / Merkus (voice), played by Jim Cummings.
Terk (voice), played by April Winchell.
(voice), played by René Auberjonois.
Tarzan & Jane is a 2002 American animated adventure film
produced by Walt Disney Television Animation.
Released on July 23, 2002, it is a direct-to-video spin-off of Disney's 1999 animated feature film Tarzan, and uses
three then-unaired episodes of the film's corresponding television series, The Legend of Tarzan.
Tarzan II, a prequel to both films, was released in 2005.
The film is set one year after the events of the first
film and Tarzan and Jane are married.
With the exceptions of Erik Von Detten and Jason Marsden as Flynt and Mungo
respectively, none of the actors from the original film reprised their roles.
The film explores themes of cartoon, tarzan, sequel, jungle.